CURRENT LOCATIONS
SEONGPANAK TEAM
HAS 5.5 KM LEFT UNTIL BAENGNOKDAM
9:10 A.M.
SEONGPANAK TEAM LEAVES SOKBAT SHELTER
Goodness.
We're still on level ground here, right?
I think so.
THEY'RE STILL ON THE EASY SECTION
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN A WHILE,
THEY FOCUS QUIETLY ON HIKING
Why are some people coming down?
They probably started early.
-They already visited the top?
-Yes.
WE'RE DESCENDING
Some people just go halfway up
to Sara Oreum Volcanic Cone.
Is that so?
THE HIKER WITH GOGGLES
SUDDENLY PROVIDES INFORMATION
I guess some just go halfway.
SARA OREUM
A VOLCANIC CONE NEAR SEONGPANAK TRAIL
IT HAS A LAKE FORMED IN ITS SUMMIT CRATER
BAENGNOKDAM
Sir, may I ask why you hike?
CAR QUIZ?
Us? For health.
For health?
To stay healthy.
And as you get older,
you have to work out your lower body more.
I SEE
In a way,
that's the most practical reason, right?
Right.
As someone once said on TV,
when one rises in position…
you tend to hear those under you less.
And when I climb mountains,
I can't hear the sounds from below.
You can't hear those below you
when you go up,
so that's why you like it?
No, that's not it.
THE RELATION BETWEEN HIKING AND LIFE
EXPLAINING WHAT IT MEANS
TO CLIMB TO THE TOP
I'm sorry,
but you're not listening
after asking questions.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Mr. Car, you only asked and…
GOT CAUGHT TUNING THEM OUT
I was listening.
I was listening to everything he said.
You were listening?
I was so deeply impressed by his words
that I was repeating them in my head.
"The higher you go,
the harder it is to hear those below."
He said that wasn't it.
Sorry?
He just said that wasn't it.
Your lower body must be fit--
That was from way before.
What about you? Are you enjoying it?
Are you enjoying hiking?
What kind of question is that?
You and I are making the same expression.
I'm sorry, but I'm sure
she likes hiking with her dad.
I mean, it's nice to come with your dad.
But I want to ask her why she hikes.
You don't really know yet, do you?
It's not my hobby, so I don't really know.
Right?
A SATISFACTORY ANSWER
She was making the same face as me.
For those who come with their parents…
when we ask why they hike,
they all say
their mom or dad made them go.
Because my mom made me go.
That's hilarious.
They were dragged there by their parents.
But I think they're really good children.
They're really nice kids.
If I was their age
and they made me go hiking…
I would've never gone.
WHY ON EARTH DO YOU HIKE?
FOR HEALTH AND PARENTS
Honestly, I didn't think
I'd be saying this today…
but it's a bit okay.
-Up to this point.
-So far.
Up to this point,
it even feels like it's pretty good.
-Really?
-We are still on the easy section.
Can't you just not say stuff like that?
9:25 A.M.
THEY PASS THE 4.75 KM MARK
I feel it now.
Now, as the path gets narrower.
The sign.
Look at the sign.
GOING FROM EASY TO MODERATE NOW
CURRENT LOCATION
THEY MUST HIKE THE MODERATE SECTION
FOR 1 HOUR AND 20 MINUTES
As long as the path doesn't turn rocky,
it should be fine.
Exactly.
It doesn't feel like it will though.
Right.
There might be some stairs.
CONFIDENTLY MOVING THROUGH
THE MODERATE SECTION
Someone wrote "Car, the garden."
What's this?
CAR, THE GARDEN
Yeah, that's me.
It's me, everyone.
SLOWLY STARTING TO SWEAT
Are we actually getting better?
Our standards
must've been raised too high.
Seoraksan was…
Damn…
Well, I shouldn't say that.
Seoraksan was definitely a tough mountain.
Hallasan is doable.
If you come to Jeju Island,
it's worth climbing once.
Okay, this is so nice.
You can do it.
What's this?
HIKERS WITHOUT SHIRTS ON
RUNNING DOWN THE MOUNTAIN
Gosh, so young and cool.
You can do it.
It's Car, the garden! Hello.
-You can do it.
-That's amazing.
That's so cool.
Look at them.
I love you!
-I love you too.
-Very cool.
Good luck.
They're so cool.
They're so passionate.
I've received passionate support
from men in their twenties.
They go crazy for me.
I think I get
a lot of love and support from men.
But I'm not sure if it's love…
or if they just want to mess with me.
But it's fine either way.
MEANWHILE, THE GWANEUMSA TEAM
WALKING THROUGH THE HARD SECTION
THE UPHILL CLIMB NEVER ENDS
Geez.
This is tough.
I really wanted to quit the show.
THE PATH KEEPS GETTING STEEPER
AND THEY KEEP BENDING LOWER
AS THEY KEEP CLIMBING WITHOUT REST
SMILES DISAPPEAR FROM THEIR FACES
GRUNTS
Damn it.
ON THE MERCILESS INCLINE
THEIR STAMINA RUNS OUT
Let's rest up there.
It's hot.
9:30 A.M.
THEY TAKE A SHORT BREAK
BOTH HUNCHED OVER
DOWOON TAKES OFF
HIS LIGHTWEIGHT PADDED JACKET
Geez.
Gosh.
Goodness.
YOON DORAEMON'S BAG IS FULL
Give me some of the food.
I'll put it in my bag.
The food is at the very bottom. It's okay.
Can you put this inside then?
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Here.
INTO TARZZAN'S BAG
It fits perfectly.
Thanks.
LAST-MINUTE REFUELING WITH SNACKS
-Clif bar?
-Yes.
9:40 A.M.
SETTING OFF AGAIN AFTER A SHORT BREAK
-Let's go.
Dowoon, you go first.
You go first. I'm a bit slow.
CURRENT LOCATION
GAEMIDEUNG RIDGE
WHAT'S LEFT NOW IS THE SECOND CRUX
DRONE FILMING WAS ALLOWED AFTER DISCUSSION
WITH HALLASAN NATIONAL PARK
GAEMIDEUNG
THE AREA WHERE THE RIDGE IS SHAPED
LIKE AN ANT'S BACK
A STEEP INCLINE
A LONG RIDGE
ONCE THEY PASS THE RIDGE,
THEY'LL ARRIVE AT THE SAMGAKBONG SHELTER
THEY ENTER
WHERE GAEMIDEUNG'S INCLINE STARTS
This is pretty intense.
Damn it.
WITH A TOUGH INCLINE
THEY KEEP THEIR EYES DOWN
AND MARCH AHEAD
I found Gaemideung so annoying.
Gosh, Dowoon.
DEEP EXHALE
My calves are about to burst.
WHAT WERE YOU THINKING
WHEN YOU WALKED THROUGH GAEMIDEUNG?
I thought…
"Why did I agree to do this?"
The ridge just wouldn't end.
No matter how much we walked,
we were still on it.
I thought, "Ants are supposed to be small.
Why is it so big?"
"They named it so strangely."
Man, I really miss…
going downhill.
HE HAS NO ENERGY TO REPLY
How much is left until the shelter?
No, don't think about it.
-Thinking is a luxury.
-I'm hungry.
I can't wait to eat.
THE MERCILESS RIDGE
TEASES AN END THAT DOESN'T COME
MEANWHILE, THE SEONGPANAK TEAM
IS PASSING THE MODERATE SECTION
I'm starting to feel it now.
Gosh.
EXCLAIMING
PRODUCER NAH AND CAR, THE GARDEN
ARE STARTING TO STRUGGLE
You can raise your hand
whenever you want to rest.
Okay.
Can we rest at the next area with benches?
-Sure.
-Okay.
IT WAS NAH WHO WANTED TO REST
I see a sort of deck area there.
Good, a deck sounds nice.
Shall we sit down for a bit?
THEY FIND A SHELTER ON THE HILL
It's so steep here.
It feels a bit like Seoraksan here.
This is pretty tough.
AFTER THE INCLINE,
THEY ARRIVE AT THE SHELTER
Should I give the other guys a call?
-Will they pick up?
-I don't think they have a signal.
I wondered if they were surviving
and if they were climbing all right.
I called to check on them,
but I couldn't reach them.
I thought,
"They must be having a hard time."
THEY ARE HAVING A VERY HARD TIME
If we go 1.2 km more…
1.2 KM AWAY FROM THE JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
Since it's 1.2 km,
it should take about an hour, right?
Then, wouldn't we make it in 40 minutes?
Who do you mean by "we?"
If it weren't for you, we could go now.
HIKERS HAVE HAD HEART ATTACKS HERE
DON'T OVERDO IT AND TAKE IT SLOW
PRODUCER NAH IS SHOCKED
9:58 A.M.
THEY SET OFF AGAIN
HOLDING ONTO THE ROPE FOR THE TOUGH PATH
SIGHING
EXCLAIMING
I can still manage.
CHAE-MIN STILL HAS ENERGY
This is still fine. It's okay.
CAR, THE GARDEN IS SLOWLY GETTING TIRED
Nice.
Tell me anytime you want.
Or I'll say it first.
Does leaning for one minute
count as resting too?
-Okay.
-Yes.
-That's a rest too?
Then, I want to rest.
NAH SAYS IT FIRST AGAIN
-Let's take a break.
-It's coming.
I'm starting to feel annoyed.
It's building.
My calves are starting to cramp now.
Really?
We took a lot of breaks
thanks to Producer Nah.
When we started to feel like this,
we took a break.
So whenever I was the only one
groaning and pausing,
you could see that I stopped.
But whenever I'd get to that point,
he'd go, "I want to rest."
So it looked like I had no choice
but to rest because of Producer Nah,
and I got to rest.
-Let's go.
-Shall we?
Yeah.
I can freely ask for these short breaks
without worrying, right?
Of course.
You can ask every minute too.
CONSIDERATE OF OLD NAH AND WEAK CAR
These breaks are perfect.
Just a moment to let the blood circulate.
Yes. Just stopping for a bit helps.
FIVE MINUTES LATER
Let me take a moment here
-to tie my shoelaces really quick.
-Sure.
I'll just tie my shoelaces.
Okay.
A DEEP EXHALE
-Did they come undone?
-Yes.
You don't need to know.
You only need to know
if I need to tie them.
Producer Nah and Car, the garden
were less exhausted than usual,
but they still felt tired,
so we took frequent breaks.
Car, the garden
was especially passionate this time.
He could've rested longer,
but most times he said, "Let's go now."
10:11 A.M.
700 M LEFT UNTIL JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
We actually can get there soon if we push.
Gosh, this might be the steepest hill.
Let's be honest and speak up
if you want to rest.
ENTERING AREA WITH STEEP STAIRS
-It's here.
-Yeah.
EVEN STEEPER
-It's here.
-Should we rest?
Shall we take a break here?
Yes. Gosh.
Chae-min, you must be tired.
No, that's not it.
-But for one last time--
-I won this time.
Yes, you won.
You lost to Producer Nah?
FIGHTING AND WINNING BY HIMSELF
You lost in the end.
Before we got to the hard section,
I thought, "Let's recuperate for a bit
and set off again."
If we just climb this part, is it over?
-Pretty much.
-We're almost there.
This may be today's most grueling part.
But Chae-min, how long do we have to
keep resting for you?
AT A LOSS FOR WORDS
My sweat's already cooling.
Shall we go up?
-You…
-Okay, let's start climbing.
It's hard to hike with a kid.
I'm sorry.
I've cooled down because of you.
Should we pick up the pace?
We have our own pace too, Chae-min.
UNGRATEFUL OLD NAH AND WEAK CAR
Athletic people like us…
SNORTING
…have our own rhythm.
Is that so?
THE FINAL INCLINE
Are these actually stairs?
-I think so.
-But they're buried under snow?
That's right.
SHOCKED
Gosh!
Is this a StairMaster?
ATHLETIC MAN 1 BREATHES HEAVILY
ATHLETIC MAN 2 BREATHES HEAVILY
CHAE-MIN IS HUMMING TO HIMSELF
This might be the end
of the steepest hill.
I think this is the end.
It feels flat now.
If only Chae-min didn't ask
for a break earlier…
Did I mess with your pace?
You messed up the tempo a bit.
I guess I killed it.
I wasn't going to mention it.
Thank you.
But please remember that
we're all athletic guys.
You win.
Remember that we're strong, muscular men.
Got it.
If you make sportscars go slow,
imagine how hard…
Our bodies can't cope with that.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I should've read the room better.
It's okay because you're nice.
That's right.
We're not scolding you or anything.
It's not a scolding.
I used to really like him.
I really like Producer Nah.
But yesterday, he said stuff like,
"Chae-min wanted to rest.
We'll go easy on you.
We'll match your pace."
He kept saying that.
But he was the biggest problem.
It's hard to match their pace.
MEANWHILE, GWANEUMSA TEAM
IS STILL WALKING OVER GAEMIDEUNG
Three hundred meters.
CURRENT LOCATION
300 M TO SAMGAKBONG SHELTER
Let's go, Dowoon.
We're so close to eating food.
Fifteen minutes?
-Fifteen minutes is…
-Should we push it?
Let's reduce it to ten minutes.
THE BEST MOTIVATION IS HUNGER
I'm hungry.
-Fifteen minutes.
-Sorry?
Fifteen minutes. Nice.
We're almost there.
You can do it.
They're celebrities.
-You can do it!
-Let's go!
-Tarzzan!
You're so handsome!
So this is how you get closer
through hiking.
I'm feeling energized.
Those soldiers are amazing.
I know, right? They don't even have poles.
All I remember
are the Special Forces soldiers.
They were so cool.
THE ENERGY THEY GOT FROM THE SOLDIERS
BOWING
SHARING THE ENERGY WITH OTHER HIKERS
This is nice.
I see something.
-I think we're here.
-Right.
We're here.
AT THE END OF THE BRUTAL ASCENT
IT FEELS LIKE A GIFT
GWANEUMSA TRAIL'S ONLY SHELTER
SAMGAKBONG SHELTER
A RESTING PLACE FOR HIKERS
WHOSE GOAL IS TO REACH BAENGNOKDAM
THEY RECUPERATE
FOR THE JOURNEY THAT REMAINS
AND REST WITHOUT LEAVING A TRACE
NO LEFTOVER RAMYEON SOUP CAMPAIGN
AND THE SYMBOL OF THIS PLACE,
SAMGAKBONG
A ROCKY PEAK FORMED BY VOLCANIC ACTIVITY
AT THE END OF THE FOREST PATH
IT SIGNALS THE BEGINNING
OF THE HIGH GROUND
THE WAY TO THE TOP
THE FINAL GATEKEEPER
AT THE PASSAGE TO THE TOP
BELOW, THE WATERS OF JEJU
COVERED IN A SEA OF CLOUDS
THEY WILL EAT HERE AS PLANNED
10:24 A.M.
THEY ARRIVE AT SAMGAKBONG SHELTER
We made it in three hours.
30 MINUTES EARLIER THAN EXPECTED
Let's eat quickly.
Quickly?
I mean, let's eat slowly.
IT WOULD BE A SHAME TO EAT QUICKLY HERE
OUTSIDE THE SAMGAKBONG SHELTER
SAMGAKBONG IS AT THE FRONT
AT THE BACK IS THE PERFECT SPOT
FOR LOOKING AT THE SEA OF CLOUDS
THEY PREPARE TO EAT RIGHT AWAY
TARZZAN HAS SOUPLESS INSTANT NOODLES
How does this work again?
I've done this before.
DOWOON HAS A SEAWEED SOUP MRE
-"Heater package."
-Open this first.
Right.
THEY QUICKLY PREPARE THE FOOD
TARZZAN'S JJAJANG RAMYEON IS READY
Dowoon, have a bite first.
You go ahead.
STILL MAKING THE MEAL
HIS FIRST PROPER MEAL OF THE DAY
YUM
FOOD FROM FLAT GROUND TASTES SWEET
ON THE MOUNTAINSIDE
I feel much better now.
I was so hungry.
DOWOON TAKES A BITE TOO
YUM
-It's good.
-Yes, it's good.
It looks delicious.
This is amazing.
HOT AND STEAMING SEAWEED SOUP
YUM
ANOTHER BITE
-Is it good?
-Yeah.
Is the seaweed soup amazing?
Try some.
It's hot.
EXCLAIMS
It's delicious, Dowoon.
Take a look at the view behind you.
Can't you see the sea of clouds?
The clouds in the sky?
THE CLOUDS ON THE HORIZON
It looks like we're on a plane.
WHO CARES ABOUT THE SEA OF CLOUDS?
TARZZAN WAS VERY HUNGRY
FINISHES EVERY LAST DROP OF THE SOUP
We're all done eating.
HE FINISHES HIS MEAL
BY EATING ALL OF HIS RAMYEON
MEANWHILE, SEONGPANAK TEAM
ARRIVES AT JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
Do you want to eat a gimbap roll?
Would you like some gimbap?
-Sounds good.
-Okay.
Thank you.
-Let's share it.
-Yes, let's share.
GIMBAP ACQUIRED
A BITE OF GIMBAP WHILE THE RAMYEON COOKS
Gimbap is the best.
Cold gimbap tastes so good.
EVEN COLD GIMBAP TASTES DELICIOUS
ON HALLASAN
Let me try the beef bone soup ramyeon.
CAR, THE GARDEN
PICKED BEEF BONE SOUP RAMYEON
It's hot.
Yours is really hot.
This looks impressive.
CHAE-MIN PICKED
IMPRESSIVE-LOOKING JJAJANG RAMYEON
HE FINISHES ALL OF THE SOUP
AND A BITE OF GIMBAP
I'll give this a try.
You're eating this
on top of the gimbap and ramyeon?
-Yeah.
-Seriously…
Is it okay to eat this much?
EATING A LOT DESPITE THE QUESTION
You know, he really eats a lot.
At that shelter…
he ate the seaweed soup,
the beef bone soup ramyeon,
and a roll of gimbap.
He's someone who'd never leave
any leftover ramyeon soup.
He's the epitome of that campaign.
NO LEFTOVER RAMYEON SOUP CAMPAIGN
If you want ramyeon with soup, bottoms up.
YOU EAT ALL OF THE RAMYEON ON HALLASAN
I finished the soup.
CLEANING UP AFTER THEMSELVES NEATLY TOO
Honestly, I think we can have some fun
before going to sleep tonight.
SEONGPANAK TEAM FEELS RELAXED
Let's go.
11 A.M.
THEY LEAVE JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
Nice, this is the way to the summit.
1 HOUR AND 30 MINUTES TO BAENGNOKDAM
ESTIMATED ARRIVAL TIME
12:30 P.M.
I think this is the perfect time to go.
There aren't many people
going up right now.
NOT MANY PEOPLE AROUND
NICE WEATHER
AND A SMOOTH PATH
It's fine this time.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Isn't it like how people say
you shouldn't push yourself
when running, Producer Nah?
Right?
If you do,
you won't go running the next day.
So, this is just the right pace for us.
Right.
We shouldn't overdo it.
SEONGPANAK TEAM IS HIKING
WITHOUT OVERDOING IT
Also, you're helping the other hikers.
-Do you know why?
-Why?
Female hikers smile when they see you.
It isn't easy to make people smile
when they're hiking.
No, it's the beautiful view around us.
You're doing something amazing.
DOING SOMETHING GREAT ON HALLASAN
I think all the guys are getting
their dopamine from seeing you.
I'll be in charge of the men.
But if you're a man
who's popular with men…
It's the most useless thing.
We passed the 1,600 m mark.
SEONGPANAK TEAM REACHES
1,600 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
Let's take a short rest.
GWANEUMSA TEAM LEAVES FOR BAENGNOKDAM
Thank you.
ALREADY LOOKING EXHAUSTED
Oh, dear.
HE SPOTS SOMETHING
It's narrow here.
ENOUGH FOR ONLY ONE PERSON TO WALK THROUGH
SLIPS
SLIPPERY DUE TO SNOW PILED UP TO THE POSTS
TRAFFIC CAUSED BY MOVING IN SINGLE FILE
Be careful. It's slippery.
NOT STAYING ALERT
EVEN FOR A MOMENT IS DANGEROUS
Stay to the right as much as you can.
PAST THE TRICKY, NARROW DOWNHILL PATH
THEY ENTER A FLAT AREA AGAIN
We came all the way up.
Exactly.
But we're going down again.
DOWNHILL AGAIN
THE DOWNHILL WALK ENDS
This is nice.
AND WHAT'S WAITING FOR THEM IS
YONGJINGAK SUSPENSION BRIDGE
CROSSING THE DEEP VALLEY
OF YONGJINGAKGYEGOK VALLEY
IS A BRIDGE 50M LONG
AND 1,560M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THE VIEW OF THE RIDGE
THAT STRETCHES TO BAENGNOKDAM
BUT IT SWAYS, SO BE CAREFUL
APPROACHING YONGJINGAK SUSPENSION BRIDGE
LAUGHING
They're giving us a thumbs up.
WHILE PASSING THE FRIENDLY HIKERS
THE BRIDGE SUDDENLY STARTS SWAYING
-Wait, Dowoon.
-What?
The bridge is shaking.
I have a fear of heights.
THIS BRIDGE
IS HANGING HIGH ABOVE THE VALLEY
IT ALSO SHAKES
AND MAY TRIGGER A FEAR OF HEIGHTS
Slow down.
Don't look down.
Look up.
SCARED
SLOWLY
SUDDEN DECREASE IN SPEED
Want to hold onto the railing?
Take your time.
FROM TARZZAN'S CAM
SPOOKED
DIFFICULTY FOR MOST: EASY
DIFFICULTY FOR TARZZAN: HARD
CAN'T TAKE HIS EYES OFF OF HIM
You crossed the shaky bridge.
Do you remember the view from there?
The view? No, I don't remember.
ALL HE SAW WAS A SCARED TARZZAN
Chae-won was a bit scared.
He has a fear of heights.
But if that's the case,
Chae-won is amazing.
Hallasan is really high.
He must've been scared,
but he overcame it.
QUICKLY CHANGING IT TO A COMPLIMENT
I didn't know
the bridge would shake so much.
I survived.
He's so cute.
THEY ARRIVE SAFELY
I'm most scared of those kinds of bridges
and transparent elevators.
AS SOON AS THEY CROSS THE BRIDGE,
IT'S AN UPHILL WALK AGAIN
That's Baengnokdam over there.
-Where?
-It's in front of you.
FACING A NOW NEARBY BAENGNOKDAM
THE REAL CHALLENGE STARTS NOW
CURRENT LOCATION
NOT THE BEST PLACE
TO CATCH THEIR BREATHS
AN ENDLESS STRETCH
OF STEEP STAIRS FOR AN HOUR
NOTORIOUS FOR MAKING HIKERS BREATHLESS
WANGGWANREUNG
THE FINAL STRETCH OF HELLISH STAIRS
TO BAENGNOKDAM
ENTERING THE GATES OF HELL
RECHARGING HIMSELF WITH GUMMIES
FROM THE START
You ate them as you walked.
Yes, it's like when you drive
for five hours or so.
You keep eating snacks without thinking.
It's something like that.
ON THE STEEP PATH
HE FUELS HIMSELF WITH GUMMIES
STARTING HIS ENGINE
ACCELERATES
PANTING
SLOWS DOWN
ACCELERATES AGAIN
ALTERNATING BETWEEN ACCELERATING
AND SLOWING DOWN
It's 5-28.
Damn it.
SIX SECTIONS LEFT
UNTIL BAENGNOKDAM AT 5-34
1.5 KM LEFT
GRUNTING
DEEP EXHALE
TRUDGING
Stairs like these…
We're going to cross
an endless stretch of stairs now.
If you get tired halfway, you can rest.
Let us know.
Okay.
-Tell us.
-Okay.
It's a very steep hill here.
The hardest part will appear soon.
THIS IS JUST THE ENTRANCE
MEANWHILE, TARZZAN IS HAVING
AN ESPECIALLY HARD TIME
HE TAKES OUT THE GUMMIES AGAIN
THEY SHARE THE GUMMIES
SETTING OFF AGAIN
YUM
The gummies helped a lot.
The ones Dowoon gave me.
You know, when I ate one
just as I wanted to take a break…
I could see clearly again.
YUM
BOOST FROM GUMMIES ACTIVATE
THEY KEEP WALKING
INCLINE SO STEEP
ONLY TOPS OF HEADS ARE SEEN BEHIND YOU
CLIMBING ALMOST VERTICALLY
THE HIKERS IN FRONT OF THEM
ARE TAKING A SHORT BREAK
PANTING AND WALKING PAST THEM
Damn.
This is no joke.
Gosh.
EVEN THOUGH THEY'RE TIRED,
THEY CONTINUE HIKING
EXHALING
THEY KEEP WALKING
WITHOUT ASKING FOR A BREAK
11:38 A.M.
THEY REACH 1,600M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THE INCLINE GETS STEEPER WITH ALTITUDE
THOSE GOING DOWN ARE STRUGGLING TOO
There were too many uphill sections.
It was an uphill climb all the way.
I think everything after the shelter
was hard.
Yes.
It was all hard for me.
But we actually passed
a lot of hikers on the way.
Right.
THEY HIKED WITHOUT RESTING
BETWEEN RESTING HIKERS
PASSING BY
PASSING BY AGAIN
EVEN AFTER THAT…
THEY KEPT WALKING WITHOUT RESTING
NO STRENGTH TO EVEN LIFT HIS HEAD
MESSY HAIR
THE PRODUCTION CREW DIDN'T REST EITHER
Let's rest for 30 seconds.
The camera operators need to rest.
Okay.
THE PRODUCTION CREW HASN'T RESTED YET
AND WILL REGROUP FOR A BIT
This is no joke.
CAN PAUSE THANKS TO THEM
Gosh.
There's no end to them.
You rested a few times because I asked to,
but otherwise, you kept going.
Whenever I climb up, I think,
"Once I stop,
I won't be able to move again."
I want to keep resting.
And everyone hikes so well
that I feel bad asking to stop.
Everyone walks so fast in front of me.
So that's what it was.
You kept going without resting,
so I thought, "He's so fit."
Honestly, we were dying too.
But nobody showed it.
-Really?
-Yes.
It must've been tough.
Honestly, we just need to
carry our own stuff.
But everyone else, like our sound mixer…
How heavy was it again?
-Was it 25 kg?
-That's right.
Our camera operator in front of me…
Deok-hwan.
A former Special Forces soldier?
He was impressive too.
I realized I really shouldn't complain.
THEY DIDN'T STOP
SO THE CREW DOESN'T SUFFER
Are you done? Give it to me.
Here. Drink this.
-Thank you.
-No worries.
CATCHING THEIR BREATHS WITH A SIP OF WATER
I miss Car, the garden.
Me too. He would've collapsed here.
THE TOUGH TRAIL
REMINDS THEM OF THEIR WEAKEST FRIEND
CAR, THE GARDEN IS GOING STRONG
The snow is melting here.
Look to your left.
What's that?
It's so beautiful.
That's incredible.
THE SEA OF CLOUDS IN FRONT OF THEM
Just a moment. I'd like to take a picture.
Good luck.
It's so beautiful.
Jung-won, let me take your photo.
Okay.
It's really beautiful.
It feels like I'm above the clouds.
This is amazing.
THEY GET THE BEST VIEW
OF THE CLOUDS
It was like a painting.
You got the view
of Jeju Island next to the sea,
and there was a bunch
of clouds above that.
It felt like Hallasan was welcoming us.
THE VIEW THAT HALLASAN WELCOMES YOU WITH
This is unbelievable.
No way.
I get to see this view
thanks to this show.
Good job, Chae-min.
Are you feeling good this time?
No.
NEGATIVE GARDEN SHOWS UP INSTANTLY
Jung-won, you're slowly becoming negative.
No, it's because I'm so happy.
I can't even talk.
MEANWHILE, GWANEUMSA TEAM
REALLY CAN'T TALK
-Let's go.
Deok-hwan must be dying.
This is pretty much like
military training.
Just now,
a hiker was behind me.
I said, "We're filming,
so you can go first."
And they said, "No, I want to rest too."
It was a total stranger.
That's so cute.
"No!"
A DESPERATE REQUEST
That means it's not just us.
Everyone else…
Everyone is…
THOSE AT THE BACK PAUSE TOO
Everyone is passing out.
THOSE IN FRONT
STRUGGLE TO MOVE FORWARD AS WELL
Let's go.
THEY KEEP CLIMBING
11:45 A.M.
THEY PASS 5-29
FIVE LEFT UNTIL 5-34 AND BAENGNOKDAM
THEY'RE AT EYE LEVEL WITH BAENGNOKDAM NOW
-We're almost there.
-Wait, are we really here?
-You are.
-Thank you.
THEY JUST NEED TO CLIMB UP
THE REMAINING STAIRS
TO ARRIVE AT AN OPEN CLEARING
CURRENT LOCATION
WANGGWANREUNG HELIPORT
LOCATED ON THE RIDGE
RIGHT NEXT TO WANGGWANREUNG
A HELIPORT
FOR EMERGENCY TRANSPORT AND SEARCH
GWANEUMSA TRAIL'S FINAL REST AREA
BEFORE BAENGNOKDAM
Tarzzan.
Good luck. You can do it.
-Thank you.
-You can do it.
Thank you.
HE ARRIVES AT THE HELIPORT
WHILE BEING CHEERED
-Dowoon.
-This is crazy.
A BIT EARLY BUT A HIGH-FIVE TO CELEBRATE
I'm so exhausted.
Where is Baengnokdam?
Over there.
We need to go there.
That is Baengnokdam.
BAENGNOKDAM
There's a lot left to go.
SIGHS
I'm really running out of stamina now.
What's "seminar"?
I said, "stamina."
Oh, stamina.
HE NEVER CHANGES
My stamina is just…
AND ANOTHER PERSON
WHO'S RUNNING OUT OF STAMINA HERE
Look at Seon-u.
It's summertime for him.
THE MAN WITH THE 25 KG BAG
LAUGHING
Seriously though,
you'll succeed in everything you do.
You're so mentally strong.
Seriously, he'll succeed
in anything he tries.
This show pushes the production crew
to their limits.
They have my full respect.
The last bit.
It'll take about 30 to 40 minutes.
ABOUT 1.25 KM TO BAENGNOKDAM
11:51 A.M.
THEY DEPART WANGGWANREUNG HELIPORT
Look at the clouds.
Gosh.
Gosh, the clouds. Over there.
They're below us. Look back there.
THEY GET A SENSE OF THE ELEVATION
FROM THE VIEW
Aside from planes,
I haven't been anywhere this high before.
BUT IT'S TOO SOON TO BE SURPRISED
THEIR DESTINATION, BAENGNOKDAM,
IS THE HIGHEST PLACE YOU CAN SET FOOT ON
SINCE IT'S RIGHT IN FRONT OF THEM,
THERE'S NOT MUCH DISTANCE LEFT
GROANING
Damn it.
THE PROBLEM IS
THEY DON'T HAVE MUCH STAMINA LEFT EITHER
It's 5-30.
11:56 A.M.
THEY PASS 5-30
REMAINING DISTANCE IS 1 KM
Damn it.
GROANS
EXHALING
DEEP BREATH
A DUET OF GROANING CONTINUES
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM
DOESN'T EVEN HAVE TIME TO LOOK BACK
It's so beautiful.
SEONGPANAK TEAM ENJOYS
THE VIEW BEHIND THEM
I bet it'll look beautiful on Baengnokdam.
Is that Baengnokdam?
Yes, it's up there.
We came up really high.
BAENGNOKDAM
We're almost there, but it looks high.
This is so beautiful.
It's so nice
that I don't regret coming up.
BAENGNOKDAM IS RIGHT AHEAD
What a nice view.
THEY HIKE WITH THE SEA OF CLOUDS
BEHIND THEM
This is incredible. It feels like the US.
THE VIEW IS INCREDIBLY STUNNING
REACHING FOR HIS POCKETS
UNBELIEVABLY, CAR, THE GARDEN
TAKES A PICTURE
This looks pretty nice.
You don't get many chances like this.
HALLASAN MAKES CAR TAKE PICTURES
Usually, all you can see is the trail.
The rest is covered in fog.
-Really?
-Usually.
If that was the case today,
I would've felt so annoyed.
Right.
-Seriously.
-Yeah, after all that.
A FOGGY HALLASAN SOUNDS TERRIBLE
Actually, I don't feel annoyed today.
I feel good.
We have 800m to go.
LET'S HAPPILY HIKE
THE REMAINING 800M TO THE TOP!
BOTH THE SNOWY PATH
AND WOODEN STAIRS
I can see the end.
Hallasan.
Let's settle things today.
It saps your energy one last time.
Gosh, this is so…
nice.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
HE DOESN'T MEAN IT
The path is paved really well here,
but it still feels a bit like Seoraksan.
I agree.
It's basalt.
THE FIRST HURDLE RIGHT BEFORE THE SUMMIT
A BASALT SLOPE
AS EXPECTED OF JEJU ISLAND,
THE ROCKY PATH IS MADE OF BASALT
There are rocks at the end?
That makes me angry.
It's so steep here.
This section is tough.
THE LONGEST AND MOST BRUTAL PATH
OF SEONGPANAK
We've walked so much
but still haven't reached.
Just when you think it'll end, it doesn't.
THE STEEP PATH NEVER ENDS
Are we here? This last part is rough.
HOLDING ONTO THE ROPE AS THEY SLOWLY CLIMB
There are a lot of people.
There are so many people up here.
THE SECOND HURDLE RIGHT BEFORE THE SUMMIT
ONE PATH BUT MANY PEOPLE
THE CLOSER YOU ARE TO THE SUMMIT,
THE MORE PEOPLE YOU FIND
It's so cold.
I need my padded jacket.
THE THIRD HURDLE
COLD WIND
It's cold now that we're up here.
AS THE HIGHEST MOUNTAIN IN KOREA,
IT GETS COLDER THE HIGHER YOU CLIMB
Are they actually lined up?
They're in line to take pictures
of the summit marker.
Really? That's crazy.
A FEW STEPS AWAY
FROM THE SUMMIT OF HALLASAN
WILL THEY HAVE
A CLEAR VIEW OF BAENGNOKDAM?
Is this it?
Amazing.
BAENGNOKDAM
THEY FINALLY MEET A CLEAR BAENGNOKDAM
This so nice.
What is this?
The crater of a volcano.
CRATER FORMED ABOUT 16,000 YEARS AGO
LOCATED 1,950M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THE CRATER LAKE AT THE SUMMIT OF HALLASAN
CONSISTS OF VARIOUS VOLCANIC ROCKS,
SUCH AS BASALT AND TRACHYTE
DESIGNATED AS SCENIC SITE NUMBER 90
THE PLACE CLOSEST TO THE SKY
They say you need three generations
of luck to see Baengnokdam.
I guess some people
must've done a lot of good deeds.
But I think all of this
was thanks to the production crew.
It was thanks to the unsung heroes.
Thanks to our producers, we got to see it.
It's beautiful.
It is pretty cool.
HE TAKES A PICTURE BECAUSE IT'S COOL
It was a bit of a shame
since the lake wasn't there,
but it was still beautiful.
"HEAVENLY HERMITS COME DOWN TO BAENGNOKDAM
RIDING WHITE DEER TO DRINK WATER"
IMHAPILGI, 1871
WHEN THE SNOW MELTS,
IT TURNS INTO A CLEAR LAKE
BAENGNOKDAM TAKES ON MANY FORMS
SEONGPANAK TEAM REACHES BAENGNOKDAM
IN 4 HOURS AND 30 MINUTES
It feels cold now.
Are Tarzzan and the others not here yet?
Why aren't they here?
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM IS STILL ON ITS WAY
-Damn it.
-Can we take a photo?
Okay.
GROANING
GRUNTS
One, two, three.
A PHOTO WITH THE SEA OF CLOUDS BEHIND THEM
AFTER TAKING A PHOTO,
THEY RESUME CLIMBING UP
12:12 P.M.
THEY PASS 5-32
ONLY 500M LEFT TO BAENGNOKDAM
Damn it.
Geez.
THE GROANING DUET STARTS AGAIN
Damn it.
GROANS
THE GROANING SOLO CONTINUES AS WELL
You kept cursing, Dowoon.
I didn't go that far.
The furthest I went was "Damn it."
I really did quit swearing.
It's like this.
When people work in the fields,
they say stuff like "heave-ho."
That's what it is.
ENTERING THE LAST SET OF WOODEN STAIRS
AS THEY SPEED UP
The Seongpanak team has just arrived.
What?
We should arrive in ten minutes too.
They arrived already?
SEONGPANAK TEAM
ARRIVED EARLIER THAN EXPECTED
Hey, that was faster than this trail.
We weren't going slow at all though.
No, we're going fast.
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM IS 30 MINUTES EARLY TOO
It's 5-33.
There's only one left until 5-34.
5 HOURS PASSED, 12:26 P.M.
THEY PASS 5-33
How many meters was it between signs?
It's 250 meters.
You're almost there.
Gosh, thank you.
That's the summit.
-Thank you.
THE LAST FLIGHT OF STAIRS
We're here.
Damn it.
GWANEUMSA TEAM ARRIVES AT BAENGNOKDAM
CURRENT TIME
12:30 P.M.
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM
COMPLETES THEIR GOAL IN SILENCE
THEY HEAD STRAIGHT TO SEE BAENGNOKDAM
There's no water.
The water froze.
-That's supposed to be water?
-Yes.
BAENGNOKDAM IS FROZEN WHITE IN WINTER
I'll take a photo.
Sure.
A RARE INSTANCE
OF VOLUNTEERING TO TAKE A PHOTO
PICTURES OF THEMSELVES FOLLOW
THEY EACH HURRIEDLY TAKE A PHOTO
TO PROVE THEY WERE THERE
Let's go to where the others are.
THEY GO TO FIND THE SEONGPANAK TEAM
THEY QUICKLY FIND THEM
Gosh, I'm so angry!
Hey, good job.
WELCOME
-I'm so mad!
-Why?
I'm not lying when I say this.
Our trail was Seoraksan Part Two.
-Really?
-Yes.
That bad?
We said if you were with us,
you would've quit the show.
That would be true.
Why give us such hard trails?
I mean, even in running,
they say to take it easy when you start.
-It was intense.
-Really?
Why do you make it so hard for us?
Honestly, our path wasn't that hard.
Really?
It was like Taebaeksan.
Taebaeksan? Ours was like Seoraksan.
Ours was like Seoraksan.
-Man, at the end…
-Like Seoraksan?
WHAT WAS IT LIKE WHEN YOU MET THEM?
I thought it must've been tough for them.
Yes.
Jung-won definitely looked happy.
He seemed to be in good condition,
which was good.
But to be honest,
all of them were injured,
so I couldn't be mad at them.
So…
Well, if you're still alive,
you have to carry on.
"It was like Seoraksan."
The moment I heard that, I could imagine.
"I see. Okay."
I resented the production crew a bit.
Since my wrist was hurt,
I resented you.
But then, I became grateful.
Should I set the timer
for nine minutes now?
PROMISE ONE: DESCEND IN 9 MINUTES
Okay, let's take a photo.
The older guys
make a big heart in the back.
The younger guys
sit and make a small one.
Let's take it quickly.
SUMMIT PROMISE TWO:
TAKE A GROUP PHOTO
Look as happy as you can.
Where do we look?
-At me.
-Okay.
Oh, here.
Two, three…
FEBRUARY 4, 2026
AT BAENGNOKDAM, HALLASAN
I achieved my goal.
THE ONE WHO SUGGESTED A GROUP PHOTO
A warm and happy photo of us
that's nice enough to put up on my fridge.
It's like how you take
four-cut photos with your friends.
I wanted to do something like that.
I've already become attached
to the others.
We've gone through hardships together.
I was happy with it.
Okay, let's go.
-Let's go.
-But Baengnokdam isn't in the photo.
-It's okay.
-We already saw it.
It didn't even take nine minutes.
Nine minutes?
The time to start going down.
I think we were here for 10 to 15 minutes.
Really? You got here so fast.
Let's descend.
12:40 P.M.
DESCENDING 9 MINUTES AFTER MEETING
-Let's go down.
-Good job.
LEAVING A CLEAR BAENGNOKDAM BEHIND
-Let's go.
THEY GO DOWN THE SEONGPANAK TRAIL
Hello.
You can do it.
Hey, Producer Nah,
you automatically cheer people on
when you descend.
We've been up here, so it feels good.
-You can do it!
-Good luck!
Good luck.
You can do it.
You become brighter
and more enthusiastic too.
-Right.
-"Good luck!"
Let's go!
DESCEND CLUB'S FAVORITE PART IS DESCENDING
DESCENDING SEONGPANAK TRAIL
ON A SMOOTH PATH OF WOODEN STAIRS
LAUGHING
What is it, Dowoon?
I was just thinking
how this is so different from our trail.
People were sledding down our trail.
I know, right?
Still, this is nice.
Take a good look.
This view is a really rare sight.
Okay.
I hear it's hard to see.
Yeah, we chose a great day.
This is nice.
DRONE FILMING WAS ALLOWED AFTER DISCUSSION
WITH HALLASAN NATIONAL PARK
Was it around here?
I hiked while admiring the view here.
I kept taking photos too.
Honestly, I don't regret
hiking up here…
because it's beautiful.
I got a good night's sleep,
so it was better.
Yes. I feel refreshed.
You still seem okay, Tarzzan.
TAKING A BREAK
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
TEARING UP
You seem a bit drained.
Yeah, I want to go home.
Why?
-Sorry?
-Did you hurt your knee?
Am I injured?
-These hard trails…
-He wants to go home.
Hiking today made me think.
Please don't give us hard trails.
What is this? He can't even enjoy it.
Look at his face.
DEPRESSED
It's like you're bullying him.
After taking this trail, I'm certain.
Please don't give us hard trails.
No one enjoys it.
Seriously, I'm telling you.
Today's trail. What is it?
Seong…
Seongchanseong?
LAUGHING
Seongpanak?
Seongpanak made me realize
it shouldn't be too hard.
THE COMPLAINER IS AS BUSY AS EVER
Making the show's cast suffer
is outdated now.
I'll drive on the way back.
-I'll do it.
-No.
We'll take care of you today.
BOWING
Seongpanak.
Seongpanak sounds like
the name of a post
from the Joseon Dynasty.
-Seongpanak.
-They're the ministers.
We're slaves. They're the ministers.
We're being treated well.
Right?
-Gwaneumsa is the post.
-You're not a king now.
AN N-RANK GWANEUMSA
Let me clear the path for him.
I'll clear the path.
HERE COMES TEAM GWANEUMSA
ON THE SNOWY ROAD
The Honorable Gwaneumsas are on their way.
"The Honorable Gwaneumsas."
I mean, I'm so amazed
that Car, the garden
has so much energy left.
Right.
Excuse me.
We didn't take a Polaroid photo.
Oh, right.
THEY FORGOT A SUMMIT PROMISE
-I knew I forgot something.
-Me too.
Let's take it at the Jindallaebat Shelter.
Sure.
THEY ARRIVE AT JINDALLAEBAT SHELTER
Here we go.
A BIT LATE BUT THEY KEEP THEIR PROMISE
MINISTER OF TRANSPORT IS DRAINED
Goodness, this is nice.
TAKING SOLO SHOTS
PASSING OUT THE SOLO SHOTS
-Are those instant photos?
-Is this product placement?
No, it's just…
Why do you two hike?
SUDDENLY INTERVIEWING HIKERS
I get to overcome my limits.
-That's so cool.
-That's cool.
We're doing this show
to get that kind of answer.
That's very cool.
Your limits?
-Overcoming them.
-To overcome them?
Which mountains have you hiked?
Have you been any other mountains?
Just Gwanaksan and Bukhansan.
Just the nearby ones.
A few in Seoul and then Hallasan?
This is my third attempt.
You came to Hallasan three times,
-and today's the first sunny day?
-Yes.
You don't want to lose to yourself, right?
-Right.
-We've already lost.
Quick acceptance.
No, we won today.
Let us win too.
We're going to lose again tomorrow.
-And the day after…
-What are we climbing?
We're just going to lose.
I went to your latest concert.
What?
I really enjoyed it.
When? First day or second day?
-I went on Saturday.
-Saturday?
She's a huge fan then!
SHE TURNS OUT TO BE
A BIG FAN OF CAR, THE GARDEN
Did he do a good job then?
He really…
-He touched our hearts.
-Yes.
GIVING HER HIS POLAROID PHOTO
Thank you.
All of a sudden?
It's a photo card.
It's his photo card?
It really is a photo card. An instant one.
AN INSTANT PHOTOCARD FOR A REAL FAN
They're my valued customers.
That is amazing.
That really is so cool.
You were able to overcome your own limits.
And she happens to be your fan.
THE SINGER AND FAN ARE SO DIFFERENT
She was a fan,
and they had come to my concert.
That really warmed my heart.
Thank you so much.
They're so cool.
I have nothing to give you but this.
No, you don't have to.
I've eaten a lot.
Share these with everyone.
Really? Thank you.
Let's get moving now.
1:50 P.M.
THEY START DESCENDING AGAIN
We're about a third there, right?
A third? Yes.
THE WARM AFTERNOON SUN
THE MELTED TRAIL ON THE DESCENT
"ASCENDING IS HARD,
BUT DESCENDING IS DANGEROUS"
REFER TO EPISODE 2
ENTERING THE SLIPPERY AREA
PRACTICALLY SLIDING DOWN
GWANEUMSA TEAM'S LEGS HAVE BECOME WEAK
THEY USE INERTIA TO DESCEND
WOBBLING LIKE A DASHBOARD ORNAMENT
LAUGHS
Can I take off my jacket here?
We'll rest and regroup here.
2:30 P.M.
PAUSING TO ADJUST CLOTHES
Sounds good.
-Nice.
-It's hot now.
Let's eat some chocolate.
-Sure.
SHARING CHOCOLATES FROM HIS FAN
-What's that?
-Chocolate.
-Want some?
-It's huge.
You've realized the importance of sugar.
I suddenly had a craving.
Dowoon.
YUM
THEY ALL STAND AS THEY REST
My legs stay fatigued if I don't sit down.
How are you guys still standing?
USING A FILM CAMERA
You look like you're on a hunger strike.
If we had a bamboo tree poking out…
I won't go.
Tell the supervisor to come out.
But he's doing that as the supervisor.
Right.
It's so discouraging.
He's a bit…
He keeps saying things by himself
from the back.
"Hey, tell me if anyone wants to rest."
Then, he suddenly says, "Me."
"Is there anywhere I can sit?"
We just stand and rest.
"But I have to sit."
HE'S MET SOMEONE WORSE THAN HIM
Okay.
Let's hit the shelter.
-Sorry?
-Pardon?
Let's go straight there.
Chae-min, we wasted so much time
because of you.
SHAMELESS
We took a break because of him.
But he goes, "Let's get a move on."
SHAMELESS SUPERVISOR
And his choice of words was
"hit the shelter."
He certainly chooses sexy words to use.
That annoyed me a little bit.
Our youngest members are struggling,
so I spoke up for them.
He probably can't hit it anyway.
"Let's hit the shelter."
We're halfway there.
CURRENT LOCATION
We're exactly halfway.
It's going to feel so good
on the way back home.
Inside that van.
Our accommodation this time
is really good.
Right.
I saw one room was empty.
Why aren't you using it?
Exactly. I thought Tarzzan and Chae-min
would sleep separately,
but they slept together.
We like sleeping together.
Right?
Dowoon seemed to sleep pretty comfortably.
I sleep really well.
You sleep so well on the floor.
The second floor room is the best one.
It's almost like your own private place
on the second floor.
It is, but he sleeps in a small room.
That's right.
I went to a small room,
thinking you guys would come up.
Each one of us…
We sacrificed for each other.
We're being considerate,
but it turned out a bit strange.
CHAE-MIN AND TARZZAN
1ST FLOOR ROOM
DOWOON
1ST FLOOR LIVING ROOM
CAR, THE GARDEN
2ND FLOOR SMALL ROOM
A SAD TALE
OF HOW THE BEST ROOM WAS LEFT EMPTY
-The path is nice now.
-I know.
And a nice forest appears here.
Oh, here.
We know this place.
Oh, here?
The phytoncides.
Okay.
How did you know?
We passed a place like this too.
I thought it was only on our trail.
THE MEMORABLE VIEW
OF CEDAR TREES ON BOTH TRAILS
IT FEELS NICE THE SECOND TIME TOO
Do we get a certificate
with the selfie we took earlier?
It's to prove we've been to the summit
of this mountain.
I see the building over there.
What? You're right.
ARRIVING WITH A GROAN TODAY TOO
We're here.
-Good job, everyone.
-Good job.
MOANING
3:55 P.M.
DESCENT COMPLETE
-Good job, everyone.
-Well done.
THE HIKE ENDS AFTER ABOUT 9 HOURS
GRIMACING
SUMMIT CERTIFICATES CAN BE ISSUED
AT THE VISITOR CENTER
SUMMIT CERTIFICATE
AND VISITOR RESERVATION QR CODE ISSUANCE
1. FILL OUT FORM
ON HALLASAN NATIONAL PARK WEBSITE
2. ATTACH PHOTO TAKEN AT SUMMIT AND APPLY
3. ENTER VERIFICATION NUMBER INTO KIOSK
4. PRINT OUT SUMMIT CERTIFICATE
JEJU SPECIAL SELF-GOVERNING PROVINCE
CERTIFICATE OF HALLASAN HIKING
NAME: LEE CHAE-MIN
DATE: FEBRUARY 4, 2026
HOW DID IT FEEL TO HIKE HALLASAN?
For the first time,
we hiked up and down with various people.
We cheered each other on
and exchanged greetings.
When we were going up,
those coming down said,
"Have a good hike."
THEY HIKED HALLASAN
ALONGSIDE MANY OTHER HIKERS
It created a sort of synergy.
I thought,
"People in Korea are still kind."
I felt that and it made me happy.
The Hallasan hike comforted me…
and helped me recharge emotionally.
Then, out of Seoraksan,
Taebaeksan, and Hallasan,
which mountain did you prefer?
Which did I prefer?
I'd definitely say Hallasan.
The other two mountains were…
NOTHING BUT BITTER MEMORIES
If I had to choose one to visit,
I'd go to Taebaeksan.
Taebaeksan was really beautiful.
Hallasan was…
Well…
If the trail had been better,
it would've made for a very fond memory.
But it was really tough.
I don't think I'll even pee
in Hallasan's direction again.
If you were to compare
Seoraksan and Hallasan…
Okay.
Hiking to Seoraksan's Huiungak Shelter
versus hiking Hallasan.
That's a tough one.
Seoraksan was definitely tougher.
If Seoraksan was 100 in difficulty,
Hallasan was 80.
-It's 80?
-Yes, 80.
No, make that 90.
-As of now.
-Okay.
Could you share a good tip
or trick you might have?
A good tip?
Think of it as walking slowly.
And what was it?
Prepare your trail food well.
Bringing three or four bottles of water
was a perfect amount.
Why on earth do you think people hike?
Maybe it's this.
It's like…
Right, we interviewed them.
You know,
you want to test your own limits.
-The people you met while descending?
-Yes.
Yes, for people like her,
that would be the reason.
I understand people who like it.
But I also understand those who hate it.
So I'm in the middle.
"You could like hiking because of this."
But…
I think it has to do
with your disposition.
When we asked someone why they hiked,
they said they were doing a challenge
of hiking 100 famous mountains.
So I thought,
"Does Korea even have 100 mountains?"
How's the view up there?
ON SEONGPANAK TRAIL
You're almost there.
The view is amazing today.
Why do you hike?
Why do I hike?
I'm trying to hike 100 famous mountains.
-A challenge?
-Really?
How many have you hiked?
We've done about 30.
Have you been to Seoraksan too?
-Not yet but--
-Don't go.
Our first mountain was Seoraksan.
THE HIKERS LAUGH
I really respect them.
But just before we started this interview,
I put the badge I received yesterday
on my bag.
They're like tokens of achievement
on my bag…
and I'm starting to have fun
collecting them.
SEORAKSAN, TAEBAEKSAN
To be honest…
I like being active.
I just play along
and pretend to not like it for the show.
I actually think it's not that bad.
You can like it.
Right.
I think it's not bad.
I like to exercise, so it's kind of fun.
I like looking at the scenery too.
Yes, I think hiking is fun.
While interviewing other people,
I thought, "I could agree with that."
It's a bit like…
"I want to make myself suffer.
I want to punish myself."
Perhaps those are the types of people
who hike.
"I'm on a diet, but I ate too much."
Or, "I should've done my homework today,
but I didn't."
"Then, I have to go up the mountain."
The middle schooler
and high schooler didn't say it,
but their parents
could've been punishing them.
BAENGNOKDAM, HALLASAN
Damijin.
TARZZAN'S FIRST MEAL AFTER DESCENT
They have yellowtail.
A RESTAURANT SERVING FRESH, RAW WILD FISH
A VARIETY OF GLISTENING RAW FISH
AND SPICY FISH STEW TO REFRESH THE PALATE
PLUS A VARIETY OF SIDE DISHES
IT'S READY FOR DESCEND CLUB TO EAT
AFTER THEIR EFFORTS
Gosh.
SIGHING
WINCING
EVERYONE GROANS AS THEY SIT DOWN
BUT ONE SEAT IS EMPTY
Why isn't Dowoon coming?
Three spans? 23?
Sixty-and-a-half.
FISHING FANATIC IS BUSY MEASURING SIZES
It must be around 75 cm.
-This is crazy.
-This is awesome.
-Let's eat now.
-Okay.
NO TIME TO WAIT
Let give it a taste.
Enjoy your food.
IT MAKES HIM SMILE
YUM
TAKES A BITE OF BOILED PORK SIDE DISH
DOWOON JOINS AND WORKS UP HIS APPETITE
WITH CRISPY FRIED FOOD
DIPS RAW FISH RIGHT INTO CHOJANG
AND TAKES A BITE
YUM
-This is good.
-It's good?
This restaurant is good.
Is it good?
Yeah.
You're good at finding restaurants.
VERY SATISFIED WITH TARZZAN'S CHOICES
What's this?
It's largescale blackfish.
-What?
-Blackfish?
Yeah, it's expensive.
Can you tell just from looking?
Of course. Try pointing to one.
A GAME OF "GUESS THE FISH" SUDDENLY STARTS
This? Convict grouper.
-This one.
-That's yellowtail.
This one.
That one doesn't have a name tag.
He was just reading these.
NAMES OF THE FISH
ARE WRITTEN ON THE PLATES
I couldn't see from here.
I thought so.
LARGESCALE BLACKFISH
HE TOTALLY FELL FOR IT
I'll let the spicy fish stew
boil down a bit more.
BOILED DOWN SPICY FISH STEW FOR THE END
Do you think they have ramyeon noodles?
They do.
-They do?
-Yes.
Do you want some ramyeon noodles?
PUTS THEM IN IMMEDIATELY
PUSHES THE RAMYEON IN
-I think it's cooked.
-It's cooked.
-Let's eat.
-Yeah, let's eat.
Help yourselves.
INHALING WHILE STILL STANDING
YUM
-Is it good?
-Yeah.
It definitely tastes better
with ramyeon noodles.
I've been observing you since Seoraksan.
You have legit ramyeon cooking skills.
From the way you stuff the noodles in.
-Really?
-Yeah.
BECOMES THE OFFICIAL RAMYEON MAKER
OF TAKE A HIKE!
BEEF BONE SOUP, JJAJANG, AND RAMYEON
THIS IS THEIR FOURTH RAMYEON TODAY
BUT THEY ALWAYS EAT
LIKE IT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'm so happy.
I feel better with some carbs in me now.
I'm so worried about the next mountain.
HOLLOW LAUGH
PRETENDING THEY DIDN'T HEAR HIM
Congratulations.
Your badges are here.
TRYING TO CHANGE THE SUBJECT TO HALLASAN
The badge says Baengnokdam, Hallasan.
BAENGNOKDAM, HALLASAN
This company…
Yes?
They make us clothes and badges too.
VERY HONORED
And here's the badge
for the Seongpanak team.
SEONGPANAK TEAM
19 KM
GWANEUMSA TEAM
18 KM
SEONGPANAK, 19 KM
GWANEUMSA, 18 KM
We went one kilometer further.
IN DISBELIEF
After going through all that hardship…
We went one kilometer longer.
This is really making me mad.
FEELING CHEATED OF 1 KM
Ma'am.
-Ma'am.
-Yes?
Would you like a badge?
Do you need a badge?
FREE BADGE GIVEAWAY
Excuse me. You can't resell it.
-The Baengnokdam badge.
-Thank you.
WHAT A SHAME
Okay, we'll reveal the next mountain.
-Then, shall we wrap for today?
-Okay.
Gosh, the next mountain.
For the next quest…
we're going to Ulsan.
-Hey!
-My home?
It's Tarzzan's home.
In Tarzzan's hometown,
it's the Yeongnam Alps'
three-peak challenge.
Congratulations.
What are the Yeongnam Alps?
HE ALSO HAS NO CLUE
What's that?
YEONGNAM ALPS
THEY ARE THE NINE MOUNTAINS
CLUSTERED IN THE YEONGNAM REGION
AN ELEGANT RIDGE CONNECTING NINE PEAKS
THE SIGHT IS COMPARABLE TO THE ALPS,
SO THEY'RE NAMED THE YEONGNAM ALPS
THANKS TO BEING 1,000M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THERE'S A PICTURESQUE VIEW
IN EVERY DIRECTION
THE ENDLESS EXPANSE
OF THE GOLDEN EULALIA GRASS FIELDS
IS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL PART
OF THE YEONGNAM ALPS
PEOPLE CONTINUE TO VISIT
TO TRAVERSE THE MOUNTAINS
AMONG THEM, DESCEND CLUB WILL HIKE
GANWOLSAN
SINBULSAN
YEONGCHUKSAN
DESCEND CLUB'S THIRD QUEST
YEONGNAM ALPS' 3-PEAK CHALLENGE
Hold on, that means we need to hike three.
It's up and down, up and down,
and up and down, right?
Chae-min, since when did you become
this rebellious?
The more you hang with them…
THE MEMBERS START RESEMBLING EACH OTHER
Jung-won, he said three peaks.
I'm asking ChatGPT.
I asked ChatGPT,
"Nah Yung-suk wants us to do
the Yeongnam Alps' three-peak challenge."
ASKING CHATGPT FOR ADVICE AGAIN
"Nah Yung-suk said that?
To be honest,
Nah Yung-suk wants you to do it
for just one reason.
He wants to bring out your true nature."
CHATGPT'S ANALYSIS IS FRIGHTENINGLY KEEN
"It's great content for the show,
but it's punishing for you."
You won't need to keep going
up and down mountains.
SEARCHING AND NOT LISTENING
Seven of the mountains are all connected.
How long will the entire trip take?
The whole trip will take
about eight hours.
SIGHING
THE GWANEUMSA TEAM SIGHS SIMULTANEOUSLY
Well, duration-wise,
it's similar to this one.
Yes.
Hey.
This is going to be tough.
ONE SEONGPANAK TEAM MEMBER
IS VERY ANGRY
There's no place to rest at all?
No, there are a lot
of well-managed resting areas.
It says your thighs
will get wrecked from the start.
"That's why Nah Yung-suk chose this.
The trail will show your true nature."
Then, it added a demon emoji next to it.
See? ChatGPT is accurate.
CONSULTANT'S CONCLUSION:
DEMONIC DIFFICULTY
I should ask my mom,
"Mom, where are the Yeongnam Alps?"
Call her now.
THIS TIME, THEY CALL TARZZAN'S MOTHER
IN ULSAN FOR ADVICE
-Hello?
Hey.
-Mom.
-Yeah?
Do you know where the Yeongnam Alps are?
Of course, I do.
It's near Ulsan, toward Eonyang.
We went there once when you were young.
Back then…
Did we take the car up?
No.
Did we walk up?
Of course, we walked.
Did I find it easy to hike?
That was the only time you went hiking.
Okay.
You had a really hard time.
Put me on the phone.
Hold on, Mom.
Car, the garden wants to speak with you.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hi!
-I'd like to ask something.
-Sure.
You know Producer Nah, right?
Yes.
Please report him to the police.
-He just deceived us.
-Right.
And he's making us go hiking.
Your son's skin is all red now.
It's a mess.
He's completely sunburnt.
They're taking us to the Yeongnam Alps.
-But--
-It's so nice there,
but now's not the right season to go.
CLENCHING HIS EYES SHUT
THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF CHATGPT'S ADVICE
We'll come pay a visit
to say hello to you.
ENDING THE CALL POLITELY
I'll put Tarzzan back on the phone.
Okay.
-She sounds so young.
-Mom, I love you. Bye.
-Okay, I love you.
-Me too. Bye.
She's so lovely.
MOTHER AND SON ARE VERY AFFECTIONATE
She said Tarzzan hiked them with a smile
when he was in fourth grade.
The term "three-peak" sounds so brutal.
-Exactly.
-Three peaks.
LAUGHING
COMPLETELY LOSING IT
Hey, I'm too stressed out now.
Let's go eat something sweet.
HE NEEDS IMMEDIATE SUGAR INTAKE
I'm too stressed to…
A HARD DAY BOTH MENTALLY AND PHYSICALLY
Subtitle translation by: Kim Yeeun